I I've got a comment here from a really
great new member of our society who has
totally
misunderstood what's going on and I need
to talk about it because it's it's this
is just really troubles me I don't know
why my comments on Twitch are not
getting reflected on the screen uh I
have not been disruptive kindly removed
me from the band list humble request it
makes me feel like a second class
citizen on your
streams my friends the chat that appears
at the bottom of the screen is currently
undergoing some kind of bug based on
Twitch changing their behavior either
the API broke or the application broke
and my friends and I from the community
spent about an hour trying to figure out
what the hell is going on and gave up
and we thought there's other things you
know to work on so unfortunately that
leaves a state where some people's
comments on the bottom of the screen are
showing up hello hello there and others
are not let's see if mine even shows up
okay there it goes I do not know what's
going on it has it doesn't have anything
to do with Subs I have nobody is banned
in my chat at all I removed every ban
from my entire Community every single
one so it has nothing we don't think it
has anything to do with like validation
we don't know the problem but I want to
make sure that you hear this you are not
being silenced right this is not this is
not me making the choice to do this okay
I it's one of the many annoying things
uh that I have to fight with all the
time with twitch and with their apis and
the that they do they regularly
break things sometimes they'll break it
and and all of a sudden I'll get
attacked but because people say your
stuff is broken and I'm like no this is
yet another Twitch API breaking thing um
VF table it says we don't see your
comment so here's a comment right now
that just came in on Twitch that is not
showing up on the screen and it is
annoying as hell should I just turn all
the screen comments off I could the only
reason I haven't done that is mostly
just out of
laziness um honest to God this is not
because I'm favoring you I mean I would
do that if I had too many people you
know commenting all the time we don't
have that problem so I just have to make
this video because I want you to
understand I'm not ignoring you it's
really important and and I don't want I
can see how you can think that so um um
beginning into the video yeah I usually
I usually turn off comments on the
screen when I'm making a video um
sometimes I forget sometimes it's fun
sometimes the video I can delete it if
somebody does that it's not that big a
deal and it's just a you know it's just
annoying to do it it's like clicking one
thing to make it not show up on the
screen um but the original reason for
that is because it's kind of nice to to
to have it on the screen in the video in
the in the v and stuff uh even though
anytime there's a b there's always going
to be chat history so should I even have
it there maybe I should just get rid of
it you know but you know what I am going
to get rid of it right now I'm going to
get rid of it I'm going to turn it off
until they fix it
because um well actually I see why it's
on now because all of my stream elements
stuff is all combined in with it so for
me to do that I have to go in and edit
my overlay and everything and that's a
pain in the butt so I don't get like
grade notifications or any of those
things on the screen if I turn that off
so
um yeah I don't know it'll probably be
on for a
while uh but whatever whatever I just
wanted you know bye